{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "The US emergency hotline is 911 because of the September 11th terrorist attacks.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
            "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over 100 BPM.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
            "question": "Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Music",
            "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
            "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
            "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Ash&#039;s Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "category": "General Knowledge",
            "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.",
            "correct_answer": "False",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "True"
            ]
        }
    ]
}